{
    "results": [
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Custom Category 1",
        "question": "What is Machine learning?",
        "correct_answer": "The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of manual programs",
          "The selective acquisition of knowledge through the use of manual programs",
          "The selective acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Custom Category 2",
        "question": "How many types of Machine Learning Techniques?",
        "correct_answer": "3",
        "incorrect_answers": ["5", "7", "9"]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Custom Category 3",
        "question": "Machine learning is a subset of_________",
        "correct_answer": "Artificial Intelligence",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Data Learning", "Deep Learning", "None of the above"]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Custom Category 4",
        "question": "Machine Learning is a field of AI consisting of learning algorithms that_________",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "At executing some task",
          "Over time with experience",
          "Improve their performance"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Custom Category 5",
        "question": "What is true about Machine Learning?",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Machine Learning (ML) is that field of computer science",
          "ML is a type of artificial intelligence that extracts patterns out of raw data by using an algorithm or method.",
          "The main focus of ML is to allow computer systems to learn from experience without being explicitly programmed or human intervention."
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Custom Category 6",
        "question": "In Model based learning methods, an iterative process takes place on the ML models that are built based on various model parameters, called ?",
        "correct_answer": "hyperparameters",
        "incorrect_answers": ["mini-batches", "superparameters", "optimizedparameters"]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Custom Category 7",
        "question": "Which of the following is a widely used and effective machine learning algorithm based on the idea of bagging?",
        "correct_answer": "Random Forest",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Regression", "Classification", "Decision Tree"]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Custom Category 8",
        "question": "Which of the following statements about regularization is not correct?",
        "correct_answer": "None of the above",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Using too large a value of lambda can cause your hypothesis to overfit the data",
          "Using too large a value of lambda can cause your hypothesis to underfit the data.",
          "Using a very large value of lambda cannot hurt the performance of your hypothesis."
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Custom Category 9",
        "question": "Data points have negative residual",
        "correct_answer": "if they are below the regression line",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "if they are above the regression line",
          "if the regression line actually passes through the point",
          "None of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Custom Category 10",
        "question": "In linear regression, we try to ______ the least square errors of the model to identify the line of best fit.",
        "correct_answer": "Minimize",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Change", "Maximize", "None of the above"]
      }
    ]
  }
  